<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="sheep_names">
        <item>Badger Face sheep</item>
        <item>Balwen sheep</item>
        <item>Black Welsh Mountain sheep</item>
        <item>Border Cheviot</item>
        <item>Border Leicester sheep</item>
        <item>Castlemilk Moorit</item>
        <item>Cheviot sheep</item>
        <item>Cotswold sheep</item>
        <item>Dalesbred sheep</item>
        <item>Derbyshire Gritstone sheep</item>
        <item>Devon and Cornwall Longwool</item>
        <item>Dorset Horn sheep</item>
        <item>Easycare sheep</item>
        <item>Exmoor Horn</item>
        <item>Greyface Dartmoor</item>
        <item>Hebridean sheep</item>
        <item>Herdwick sheep</item>
        <item>Jacob sheep</item>
        <item>Kerry Hill sheep</item>
        <item>Llanwenog sheep</item>
        <item>Lleyn sheep</item>
        <item>Lonk sheep</item>
        <item>Manx Loaghtan</item>
        <item>Norfolk Horn sheep</item>
        <item>North Ronaldsay sheep</item>
        <item>Portland sheep</item>
        <item>Romney sheep</item>
        <item>Rough Fell sheep</item>
        <item>Ryeland sheep</item>
        <item>Scottish Black Face sheep</item>
        <item>Soay sheep</item>
        <item>Southdown sheep</item>
        <item>Suffolk sheep</item>
        <item>Swaledale sheep</item>
        <item>Texel sheep</item>
        <item>Wensleydale sheep</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sheep_descriptions">
        <item>This sheep looks a bit like a big badger.</item>
        <item>Meaning “white blaze” in Welsh,
            the Balwen sheep is named after the distinct marking on its face.
            Traditionally this was used by farmers to differentiate their flocks
            from neighbouring flocks of Welsh mountain breeds.</item>
        <item>The striking Black Welsh Mountain Sheep is self-reliant and
            adaptable and you can expect to meet it in upland areas of Wales.</item>
        <item>The Border Cheviot\’s reputation for being hardly and alert is no surprise
            considering its thought to have developed from the sheep who swam to shore
            from the wrecked ships of the Spanish Armada.</item>
        <item>Is it a sheep or is it a rabbit? Despite looking so alert,
            Border Leicester\’s are a docile breed of sheep.</item>
        <item>Castlemilk Moorits were created in the 1900s to enrich
            Sir John Buchanan Jardine\'s estate, after which they are named.</item>
        <item>The burly Cheviot can be found up and down the UK as well as abroad.</item>
        <item>Cotswold sheep have a reputation for being calm and friendly and are
            thought to have originated from sheep kept on large Roman estates.</item>
        <item>The impressive Dalesbred is indigenous to the scenic Yorkshire Dales but
            has made its way further afield.  Its dense wool is often used to make
            carpets and occasionally tweed.</item>
        <item>Being one of the oldest sheep breeds in Britain, the sturdy Derbyshire Gritstone
            is well adapted to life in the upland Peak District.</item>
        <item>Cuddly Devon and Cornwall Longwools are said to produce
            more wool than any other British breed.</item>
        <item>The beautiful Dorset Horn sheep leaves no questions as to where it gets its name.
            Its also the only British Sheep capable of breeding through winter.</item>
        <item>The easy-going Easycare sheep was developed in the 1960s.
            It sheds its wool in summer and requires minimal veterinary care.
            Its shed fleece even decomposes to act as a natural soil conditioner.
            This might be the coolest sheep around.</item>
        <item>The Exmoor Horn descends from sheep that wandered the moors
            of Exmoor for hundreds of years.  Despite this, breeding Exmore Horn
            ewes only account for around 10% of all sheep on Exmoor.</item>
        <item>The beautiful Greyface Dartmoor can be recognised by
            its distinctive face markings.</item>
        <item>Small yet striking, the Hebridean Sheep has bounced
            back from near extinction in the 1970s.</item>
        <item>The iconic hardy Herdwick can often be found enjoying
            the Lake District with a smile on its face.</item>
        <item>Named after the Biblical figure of Jacob, the Jacob sheep is more closely
            linked to sheep from Africa and South-West Asia than other British breeds.</item>
        <item>Owing its name to the village of Kerry in Wales,
            the Kerry Hill sheep is easily recognised by the striking
            markings on its friendly face.</item>
        <item>Llanwenogs are a rare breed of sheep
            originating from West Wales\’ Teifi Valley.</item>
        <item>The adaptable Lleyn sheep is from North-west Wales and enjoys
            both upland and lowland grazing.</item>
        <item>The Lonk gets its name from the word \‘lanky\’, meaning long and thin.
            It\’s commonly found on the central and south Pennine hills.</item>
        <item>As its name suggests, the Manx Loaghton is native to the Isle of Man.
            Its also one of the rarest sheep in Britain.</item>
        <item>The Norfolk Horn is one of the oldest sheep in Britain.</item>
        <item>Named after the most Northernmost island of Orkney,
            the original semi-feral North Ronaldsay flock feeds almost entirely on seaweed.</item>
        <item>The Portland sheep remained isolated on the island of Portland while the rest
            of the UK was experimenting with breed development.</item>
        <item>New Zealand\’s impressive sheep industry is in part owed to the Romney,
            but their hardiness means they can be found all over the world.</item>
        <item>Rough Fells are one of the three breeds of sheep native to Cumbria as well as
            being one of the largest mountain breeds in Britain.
            Because of its special fleece the Rough Fell doesn\’t require housing,
            even during the harshest of winters.</item>
        <item>Considered to have some of the finest wool in Britain,
            Queen Elizabeth I insisted on only wearing stockings
            made from wool from Ryeland sheep.</item>
        <item>The Scottish Black Face is the most common sheep breed of the United Kingdom.
            Its friendly face makes it a welcome sight wherever you go.</item>
        <item>Despite their delicate gazelle-like appearance,
            Soay sheep are resilient and can survive in exceptionally
            harsh weather conditions.</item>
        <item>The bulky English Southdown sheep is the shorter counterpart to the original
            Southdown breed of the United States.</item>
        <item>The Suffolk sheep has been exported to many countries but originated
            from the Bury St. Edmunds area of Suffolk.</item>
        <item>Both friendly and hardy, Swaledales can often be found mooching around
            the Yorkshire Dales, County Durham and around the Cumbrian Pennines.</item>
        <item>Originating from the island of Texel off Holland,
            the Texel sheep is now one of the most widespread breeds in Britain.</item>
        <item>Though known for its much-loved cheese,
            the Wensleydale is also blessed in the wool department.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>